Payton Clark

Front-end Developer

Personal Info

Address

505 N. Van Buren St.

West Frankfort, IL 62896

Phone

(618) 923-1619

E-mail

payton182@gmail.com

Date of birth

1990-07-16

WWW

paytongc.cloud

Skills

HTML5 & CSS3

advanced

JavaScript

Sales & Marketing

SEO

Graphic Design

Teamwork & Communication

Critical Thinking/Problem

Solving

Emotional Intelligence

Passionate believer of technology pursuing a career in web and software development. 1+ years working with hypertext markup and object-oriented programming. Adapts and learns quickly in fast-changing environments. I have spent years assisting others adapting new practices in disruptive technologies and I hope to better develop the skills to reach larger audiences.

Experience

2014-09 - **Solutions Specialist**

present Verizon Wireless

- Trained customers and coworkers on new features of popular operating systems
- Met and occasionally exceeded monthly quotas
- Collaborated with coworkers on team-building exercises
- Cultivated positive relationships with clients, leaders, and peers

2018-06 - Freelance Web Developer

present Self-employed

- Designed website and blog layouts for friends
- Reached out to local professionals for guidance
- Designed custom art for local businesses

Education

2008-08 - **John A. Logan College**

2011-05 Associates of Arts

Additional Activities

2015-01 - **Home Studio**

present Audio Engineer

- Integrated software to solve real-world problems in a recording environment.
- Managed digital content for multiple clients on several web platforms

2004-08 - Live Performer

present Musician/Band Manager

- Perpetually learning new ways to integrate software automation and tech into discipline.
- Used industry-level software and web platforms to leverage success and profitability.